http://www.clickhere.gr/content/privacypolicy.asp

PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy applies to www.clickhere.gr, www.clickhere.fr, www.clickhere.holiday, and all subdomains thereof, such as *.clickhere.gr, *.clickhere.fr and *.clickhere.holiday.
Administrator of aforementioned websites: clickhere.gr, hereinafter referred to as the 'administrator'.
For full contact details click/tap here
For the administrator's terms of use, click / tap here
SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH A CONTACT FORM ASSOCIATED WITH A SPECIFIC ACCOMMODATION PROPERTY
On certain pages of this website, it is possible to contact the manager of an accommodation property directly, through a contact form,
to enquire for example for accommodation.
IMPORTANT: Do NOT submit sensitive personal information through the contact forms on this website, as is for example, a credit card number.
In order to stay safe, as a general rule, you should not submit through a form, information that is Not requested.Individual accommodation property webpages on this website, may link to a third party booking engine, through which you can effect online reservation and payment.For more details on this, read the section "Linking to third party websites and resources including a booking engine" on this page.
It is forbidden for persons under 16 years of age to submit personal information through contact forms on this website (such as your email, name and surname, telephone number and any other identifiable information).
By using accommodation property contact forms on this website, you submit [potentially identifiable] personal information, which includes your email, name and surname, country of origin (the above as submitted by you), user agent (i.e. anonymous device and browser info like for example Android, Mozilla, Iphone/Safari, etc.) and may include your telephone or mobile number and other personal details that you fill out.
When you submit a contact form through an accommodation property webpage, it is sent by email to the specific property's manager and the administrator. This information is kept strictly confidential unless you have granted explicit consent to act otherwise, and is used solely for the purpose of your enquiry, as is for example, a request for accommodation during a specific period.
The administrator retains copies of form enquiries submitted:
a) as a backup, in case the property manager experiences email problems, so that the enquiry can be forwarded to them if necessary
b) to ensure proper functioning of the contact form
c) to check website performance, including general statistical analysis (e.g. the total number of enquiries the website has received over a certain period) to ensure that functionality improvements are made if necessary
The administrator does not by default receive copies of subsequent correspondence between you and the property manager, unless either you or the property manager include an administrator email in a subsequent reply (for example, if you cc an email ending in @clickhere.gr.)
The administrator retains the right to contact you directly, in order to facilitate your enquiry if necessary, and for that purpose solely. For example, the administrator may at the property manager's
request, undertake to respond directly to your enquiry, if they for whatever reason, are unable to do so themselves. This however, is extremely rare.
Whenever you submit an enquiry through the contact form on an accommodation property webpage, you always have the option of requesting that all communication records either be disclosed to you, or deleted, either by the property manager, the administrator, or both.
Please keep in mind that deletion is contingent upon legal or contractual record keeping requirements.
LINKING TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES AND RESOURCES INCLUDING A BOOKING ENGINE
This website may link from specific accommodation property webpages to an outside resource (third party website) as may be for a example, a booking engine. In this case, you will be transferred to the third party's website which the property manager has contracted with directly, to enable you to carry out accommodation availability searches online and make a reservation, including payment.
The administrator thoroughly checks all third party resources this website may link to, including booking engines, to ensure they meet all necessary security and privacy requirements. As a result, this website will only link to trusted third parties. However, it is important to consult the respective, third party's privacy policy and terms of use, since it is managed by an entity outside the administrator's control.
TRAFFIC MONITORING
As is the case with any server on the Internet, traffic on this website is logged. This enables the administrator to compile anonymous statistical reports that display aggregate data. For example, total traffic by day, month, country and device type (e.g. desktop, tablet, mobile). All potentially personal / identifiable information (such as IP numbers) is kept strictly confidential and secure.
Traffic log copies are maintained offline by the administrator, on a secure system:
a) As a backup in case of data loss, should the need arise for instance, to regenerate anonymous, aggregate data reports, for the purpose of statistical analysis
b) To be able to detect malevolent activity on the website, which is an indispensable part in the ongoing effort to ensure a secure browsing environment
c) In order to comply with legal or contractual record keeping requirements
THIRD PARTY RESOURCES
Portions of this website use third party resources in order to enhance your browsing experience. A cookie notice is displayed on such subpages.
Third party resources used:
Google Maps (Google Inc.)
Google Fonts (Google Inc.)
For Google Inc.'s privacy policy click/tap here
NETWORKS USED
This website uses a number of top-tier hosting and content delivery networks in order to provide a quality browsing experience.
On every single network the administrator employs, thorough measures are undertaken in order to enhance anonymous browsing. For example, cookies are disabled where it is possible to do so without affecting the website's proper functioning.
SECURITY
As technology evolves and malevolent online practices become increasingly "creative", no company whatsoever, including the administrator, can provide a 100% guarantee that security will not be compromised in the future. As such, it is imperative that you, the user, also undertake all necessary measures to ensure your software and hardware devices are secure. This includes and is not limited to, maintaining an up-to-date antivirus on your device, a firewall, updating vulnerable hardware drivers and carrying out critical operating system updates.
Hotels in Greece
Hotel offers & deals!
